find-fm.com 2010-08-23

# Search results for: <? echo $keyword; ?>

Find.FM respects your privacy. Our purpose in collecting information from you is to help us provide you with better service, such as notifications about special offers and promotions. We will not wilfully disclose any individually identifiable information about you to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy statement. Furthermore, we do not specifically target children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly collect, without parental consent, individually identifiable information from such children.

What Information Do We Collect?

From time to time we may request that an entity making application for an account with Find.FM provide us with certain personal information (such as their name, email address, etc.) in connection with various services offered on our site. We do not collect any personal information except when an individual specifically and knowingly provides such information. When we request information, we explain how this information may be used and give you an opportunity to request that the information not be used for those purposes. We also give you an opportunity to opt out of future communications from us.

Cookies 

For account management purposes and like most sites, Find.FM uses cookies. Cookies are data files stored on your computer that identify you as a unique user. Cookies enable us to track user trends, preferences and patterns to better understand our user base and to improve the quality of our service. Most browsers permit users to refuse cookies or to be notified before a cookie is accepted. You can visit our site without using cookies.

Links to Other Sites 

Find.FM contains links to other sites. These sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Since we do not control these sites; we are not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content of such sites.

With Whom Do We Share Information? 

Find.FM may share non-personal and non-personally identifiable information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information, such as how often the average user visits Find.FM. We will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent.

Consent and Changes to this Privacy Statement 

By using our site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this privacy statement and to our Terms of Service. Find.FM may decide to change this privacy statement from time to time. When we do, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
